http://www.aaksis.org/page/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Toggle navigation
Home (current)
About Us
About Board of Directors
Education
Education Education, Medical, and Advocacy Groups Nolten Article
/ Privacy Policy
AAKSIS is aware that mere registration on the website, membership in the organization. or membership as a contributor to Friends of AAKSIS implies either a genetic anomaly or a close relationship to people or persons who have such an anomaly.The recording of names, addresses, phone numbers, e-mail addresses, karyotype information, and dates of birth or diagnosis is done to provide the registrant with newsletters, brochures, announcements, and other information related to Klinefelter Syndrome. Information is kept confidential.No directory will be published nor will the registration information ever be sold or provided to an outside party. Basic information of site registrants is periodically reviewed by AAKSIS Board members to determine the characteristics of our audience by age and relationship to XXY individuals for site modification.Scientific ReseasrchAAKSIS supports scientific research into the causes and medical and developmental complications of XXY.Should our organization be approached regarding providing subject names for a scientific survey or study, the proposal will first be studied and then approved by the AAKSIS professional advisory board.Once approval is given, AAKSIS will directly notify appropriate registrants of the possible participation. The subject may then decide whether or not to participate.One should never assume that someone identifying him/herself as a "researcher" has the approval of AAKSIS or is conducting valid research.Link to Other WebsitesThis site may contain links or references to other Web sites. Please be aware that we do not control other sites and that this On-Line Privacy Policy does not apply to those Web sites. We encourage you to read the Privacy Policy of every Web site that you visit.By using and registering on the site, you are confirming that you agree with this privacy policy. If you do not agree with the privacy policy, please do not register your name with AAKSIS.
The American Association for Klinefelter Syndrome Information and Support (AAKSIS)
Contact Us © 2020Powered by Virtual Vision Computing, LLC, All-in-One Website,Business Listing
